Finding Aid for the Louise LeQuire Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Family
  - Rollin Lasseter
    - Letters, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Lecture, “Stone Age Art: Painting, Myth, and Ritual,”, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - “Vagabond”, 1958-59 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - “A Midsummer’s Tale” (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - “Confessional” (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - “The Redoubt” (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Short Stories, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Writing, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - News Clippings (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Ruth D. Lasseter, Poetry (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Oil Paintings of Children (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Lista, Mother’s Day Card (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Engagement Announcements, 1946/1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Grandchildren (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Obituaries/Funerals (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Misc. family materials (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Home (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Artists
  - Poets
    - Poet as Critic, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Bunting, Basil (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Heaney, Seamus (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Jarman, Mark (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Milosz, Czeslaw (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Niedecker, Lorine (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Notes, Davie’s class, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Donald Davie’s English Course, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Pound, Ezra, Cantos LXXII & LXXIII (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Pound, Ezra, Clippings (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Pound, Ezra, Seminar notes, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Pound, Ezra, Seminar, 1986 (1) (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Pound, Ezra, Seminar, 1986 (2) (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Ransom, John Crowe (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Red Grooms
    - Correspondence—Incoming (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence—Outgoing (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence re: LeQuires lending Grooms Pieces, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence re: LeQuires lending Grooms Pieces, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - TSM Contracts and Correspondences (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Invitations to Grooms’ Shows/Exhibitions (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Pieces lent by LeQuires to Cheekwood (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Marlborough Gallery Invitations/Press Releases (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Draft of Article by LeQuire for New York Magazine, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Writing, Grooms, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Writing, LeQuire (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Writing, LeQuire (2) (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Film—TSM Retrospective, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - TSM Retrospective, Teacher Guidebook (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - TSM, Final Report (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - TSM, Retrospective Photos (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Film—TSM (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Film—Notes (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Film—Summary of All Income and Expenses (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Film—Polaris Entertainment, Inc. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Film—Promotion (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Film—Red Grooms Royalty Payments (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Film—Photos (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Film—Round and Round with Red, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Printed Postcards and Greeting Cards (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Misc. Photos (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Motive, March 1961 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Motive, May 1962 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Motive, May 1963 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - —Magazine Features, Gallery/Exhibition Brochures
    - Art Education, January 1969 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Art News, December 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Art and Man, vol. 6, no. 6, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Horizon, August 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - The Sciences, September 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - The Sciences, December 1980 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Portfolio, March/April 1981 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Art Voices, January/February 1982 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - New Creation Exhibit, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Red Grooms and Ruckus Manhattan, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Photos—Martin Wiley Gallery Show, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Red Grooms: A Catalogue Raisonné of his Graphic Work, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Marlborough, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Tampa Museum, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Grooms’ “Public Works: Private Patrons,” 1983 (with Tampa Museum) (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Marlborough, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Marlborough, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files—Marlborough, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Subject Files—Marlborough, 1987-89 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files—Nashville Collects Red, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Subject Files—Marlborough, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Subject Files—Marlborough, 1990 (French) (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Subject Files—The New Yorker Covers, 1992-93 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Subject Files—Wood Street Galleries, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Subject Files—Marlborough, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - —Gallery/Exhibition Brochures, New Clippings
    - Subject Files—Cheekwood, “What’s All the Ruckus About?”, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms Exhibition at Knoxville Museum of Art, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Subject Files—Carousels (Tennessee), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files—Marlborough, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files—The Human Comedy: Portraits by Red Grooms, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms, News Clippings, 1954-1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms, News Clippings, 1970-1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms, News Clippings, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms, News Clippings, Marlborough, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms, News Clippings, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms, News Clippings, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms, News Clippings, Academy Awards (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms, News Clippings, Whitney Exhibition, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms, News Clippings, 1989-1999 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files—Red Grooms, News Clippings, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - William Edmondson
    - Subject Files—Edmondson Biographical Notes, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files—Edmondson Archive/Gallery Finding Aids (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence—LeQuire Lending Pieces/Info, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence—LeQuire Lending Pieces/Info, 1982-1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files—Bernice Williams’s Tombstone (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files—Essays on Edmondson (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files—Family Interviews/Oral Histories (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files—Film Plans, no date (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Subject Files—News Clippings, 1941-1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files—News Clippings, 1981-2000 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Subject Files—New Clippings, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Subject Files—Albany Museum of Art (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Subject Files—Cheekwood Mirkels, 1964 (1) (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Subject Files—Cheekwood Mirkels, 1964 (2) (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files—Montclair Art Museum Exhibition, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Subject Files—Tennessee State Museum, Symposium notes, July 1980 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Subject Files—Tennessee State Museum—Edmondson Packet, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Subject Files—TSM Exhibition 1981, Slide Commentary (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Subject Files—Kindergarten University School Trip to Edmondson Exhibit at TSM, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Subject Files—Tennessee State Museum Retrospective, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Subject Files—Smithsonian Magazine, 1981—Edmondson Article by LeQuire (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Subject Files—Outline for book on Edmondson, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Subject Files—Obituary, November 22, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files—Cheekwood, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Subject Files—Owners of Edmondson’s Art (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Subject Files—Owners (notes) (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Subject Files—Owners’ Photos (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence re: viewing of Edmondson’s works (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Photo Negatives, Edmondson (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Other Artists, A-B
    - Accetta, Suzanne (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Adair, Virginia Hamilton (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Ailey, Alvin (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Akers, William (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Allen, Nena (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Allen, Thomas B. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Allen, Ward (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Ardon, Richard (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Assoluta, Aulenti (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Aufderheide, Patricia (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Avendon, Richard (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Avendon, Richard—Lecture by LeQuire (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, Magazine and Newspaper Clippings (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer, “From Lebrun to Bartlett: Women in Art” (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Bell, Madison Smart (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Partners—Bell and Neff, Clippings (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Benneyworth, Steve (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Benton, Thomas Hart (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Bernier/Russell couple (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Berry, Will (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Biel-Bienne, Eugene V. (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Boccioni (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Bodo, Ilona (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - —Artists, B-F
    - Bodo, Sandor (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Bodo, Sandor—Invitations to Exhibits (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Bodo, Sandor—News Clippings (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Bonnard, Pierre (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Boone, Victoria (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Braddock, Jane (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Brindley, Charles (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Brooks, George (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Brooks, Janet (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Brush, George DeForest, News Clippings (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Bryant, Olen (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Bryant, Olen—Correspondence, Incoming (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Bryant, Olen—Correspondence, Outgoing (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Bryant, Olen—News Clippings (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Bryant, Susan Hicks (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Bullock, Barbara (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - von Bülow, Sunny Crawford (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Burnett, Peggy (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Calder, Alexander (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Calk, Olin (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Calloway, Chris (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Cassatt, Mary (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Cézanne (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Charney, Sharon (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Chen, Wei-fu (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Clanton, Tonya (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Clark, Alan—News Clippings (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Clark, Edward (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Claudel, Camille—Magazine Article (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Cloar, Carroll (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Craft, Yvette (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Crouch, Ned (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Cunningham, W.J. (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Dahl-Wolfe, Louise (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Danley, Jeff (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - David, Jacques-Louis (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Davie, Donald—Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Davie, Donald—Writing (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Donald David: Poet as Sculptor—Film (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Davie, Donald—News Clippings (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - DaVinci (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Degas (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Dettwiller, Kathryn (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - DeWitt, Charles (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Diebenkorn, Richard (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Dill, Jane Ann—Correspondence, Incoming (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Dill, Jane Ann—Invitations to Exhibits (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Dill, Jane Ann—News Clippings (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Dill, Jane Ann—Writing, LeQuire (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Donelson, Mary Hooper (Donelson Family)—News Clippings (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Dowell, John E. (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Driskell, David (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Driskell, David—News Clippings (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - —Artists, D-K
    - Dury, George—News Clippings (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Eakins, Thomas (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Enrique, Mario (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Erickson, Connie—Invitations (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Erickson, Connie—Teaching Resources (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Escobar, Marisol (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Faith, Marla (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Fantin-Latour, Henri (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Frankenthaler, Helen (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Freeman, Annie (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Freeman, Annie—Correspondence, Incoming (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Freeman, Annie—News Clippings (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Freeman, Annie—Writing, Freeman (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Freeman, Annie—Writing, LeQuire (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Frostic, Gwen (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Gannon, Lee (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Gaul, Gilbert, Cheekwood (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Gentileschi, Artemisia (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Goya (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Graf, Mildred Neese (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Gray, Michael (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Grecco, Emilio (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Guider Family (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Guest, Kathryn (Kathy) (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Halperin, Richard (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Handly, Avery (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Harvey, Bessie (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Hatleberg, Jan (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Hebald, Milton (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Herbert, Chip (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Hinton, Kem G (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Hiroshige, Ando (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Holder, Kenneth (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Holland, Ed (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Holland, Paul (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Homer, Winslow (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Howell-Jones, David (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Hunter, Sherri Warner (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Hyman, Sarah (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Jacob, Ned (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Jarman, Mark (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Jefferson, Thomas (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Johns, Jasper (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Jones, Ted (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Junkin, Marion (Louise’s Art Teacher), 1945-46 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Kahn, Wolf (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Kandinsky, Wassily (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Kaye, Tom (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Kern, Mary Sue (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Knestrick, Walter (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - deKooning, Willem (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - —Artists, K-O
    - Lange, Dorothea (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Lapin, Todd (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - LaRose, Renee (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - LeDoux, David (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Lee, Hermione (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Leeper, Doris (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Leonard, Wendy (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Artist—Levy, Simon (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Artist—Lewis, Wyndham (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Lowry, Mary Helen (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - MacDonald, Ralph (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Mackie, Jack (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Maillie, Myles (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Manet, Edouard (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Matisse, Henri (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - McBride, Michael (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - McCarthy, Justin (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - McCroskey, Joyce (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - McGee, Carrie (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - McGowan, Ellen (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - McLean, Paul (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Mehaffie, Jordan (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Menzel, George (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Mestrovic, Ivan (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Meyer, John Dodge (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Mihal, Milan (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Miles, Minnie (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Miller, Harold (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Mims, Puryear (1) (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Mims, Puryear (2) (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Mims, Puryear—Public Works Refinishing Issue, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Miro, Joan (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Monet, Claude (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Monick, Susie (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Moretti (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Murphy, Marilyn (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Musgrove, Doris (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Neal, Michael Shane (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Nevelson, Louise (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Newman, Robert Loftin (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Newman, Willie Betty (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Oates, John (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - O’Keefe, Georgia (1) (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - O’Keefe, Georgia (2) (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - O’Keefe, Georgia—ArtNews (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - —Artists, O-R
    - Ondaatje, Michael (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Van Ostade, Andriaen (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Painter, Richard (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Papousek, Elizabeth (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Partee, McCollough (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Perdue, Wiley (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Perkins, Phillip (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Picasso, Pablo (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Pickup, Ernest (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - The Pointer Sisters (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Potter, Bertha Herbert (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Powers, Alex (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Prado, Jairo (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Quimbaya (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Randolph, Somers (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Reardon, Gwen (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Reid, Mike (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Remington, Frederick (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Remington, Frederick—News Clippings (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Remington Script (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Rhody, Alan—Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Rice, Tom (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Richardson, John F (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Richier, Germaine (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Ridley, Gregory (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Ridley, Gregory—Invitations to Exhibitions (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - MS Book by Gregory Ridley (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Ridley, Gregory—News Clippings (1) (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Ridley, Gregory—News Clippings (2) (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Ridley, Gregory—News Clippings and Press Releases (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - —Artists, R-S
    - Riggins, Lois (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Ritz, Joan (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Rogers, David (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Root, Peggy (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Rothenberg, Susan (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Rouault, George (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Ryman, Robert (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Sargent, John Singer (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Scott, John (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Segal, George (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Seigenthaler, John (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Sellers, Anna—Correspondence, Incoming (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Sellers, Anna—News Clippings (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Sellers, Anna—Photos (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Shanks, Nelson (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Sheats, Jamaal (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Siler, Todd—Cerebralism (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Smith, Cyril Stanley (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Smith, Peggy (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Speagle, Sandy (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Stackhouse, Richard (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Stella, Frank (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Steltmeier, Butler (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Stettheimen, Florine (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Stevens, Wallace—Lecture, “The Poem as Icon” by LeQuire (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Stevens, Walter Hollis (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Strauser, Sterling (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Strickland, William (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Stumpf, Sam (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Sublett, Carl (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Sublett, Carl—Biographical Notes (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Sublett, Carl—Correspondence, Incoming (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Sublett, Carl—Invitations (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Sublett, Carl—Exhibition, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Sublett, Carl—News Clippings (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Sublett, Carl—Photos (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Sublett, Carl—Photo slides (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - —Artists, S-Z
    - Sullivan, Walter (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Swensson, Earl—Interview (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Swensson Walker, Lin (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Takaezu, Toshiko (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Takaezu, Toshiko—Magazine Clippings (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Taylor, D.L. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Terra, Daniel J (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Thompson, Bob (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Threalkill, James (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Tiepolo (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Toole, Polly (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Truett, Meryl (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Tuck, Hinton, Everton Architects (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Verneer, Johannes (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Villon, Jacques (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - DeVries, Simonetta (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - DeVries, Simonetta—News Clippings (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Vollard, Ambroise (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Walsh, Mimi (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Walton, Tom (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Warterfield, Charlie (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Wattanapun, Wattana (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Webb, A. C. (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Wegman, William (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Welty, Eudora (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Wickham, Tanner Enoch (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Wildner, Werner (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Wise, Scott (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Wright, Dayton (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Woolwine, Marie (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Wotruba, Fritz (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Wyeth, Andrew (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Wyeth, N.C. (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Zaner, Junanne (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Zeigler, Gavin (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Zibart Siblings (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - —Media Materials
    - VHS: Donald Davie: Poet as Sculptor (1) (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - VHS: Donald Davie: Poet as Sculptor (2) (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Cassette: Donald Davie: The Pound Class (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Donald Davie Reading Pound, The Pound Class, 11/15/85 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Donald Davie Reading Pound, The Pound Class, 11/15/85 (2) (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Donald Davie Reading Pound, The Pound Class, 11/22/85 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Cassette: Tape 2 First Side: Pound Class, Rock Drill Cantos, 12/11/85 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Cassette: Tape 2 First Side: Pound Class, Rock Drill Cantos, 12/11/85 (2) (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Conclusion, Pound Class, 12/19/85 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Conclusion, Pound Class, 12/19/85 (2) (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Conclusion, Pound Class, 12/19/85 (3) (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Donald Davie, continued (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Continuation, Russia (Box 29, Folder 13)